<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rich on Bud</title>
    <link>https://sj-log.github.io/tags/Rich/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rich on Bud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sj-log.github.io/tags/Rich/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>나폴레온힐-마스터마인드-우리가-왜-모여야할까</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/%EB%82%98%ED%8F%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A8%ED%9E%90-%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/%EB%82%98%ED%8F%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%98%A8%ED%9E%90-%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/</guid>
      <description>마스터 마인드가 무엇인가 #   서로 모이는데 힘쓰라, 성경  왜 모여야할까 #   함께 꿈을 꾸는 모임 &amp;lsquo;인생법칙&amp;rsquo;에서 &amp;lsquo;꿈을 빨리 이루고 싶다면 함께 꿈을 향해 노력하는 모임에 들어가라&amp;rsquo; 마치 동호회 모임처럼, &amp;lsquo;특정 목표를 달성하기 위해 모이는 동호회&amp;rsquo; - 각자의 목표를 측정 가능한 수준으로 바꾸기 함께 모이면 시작되고, 함께 도우면 진보하고, 함께 일하면 성공한다. 헨리포드  어떻게 해야할까 #  나폴레온 힐은 오하이오 주 칸톤에 자신의 철학을 들으러온 13명에게 어떻게 하면 좋을까 고민하다, #   소모임을 갖기 모여서 용기를 북돋을 것 성장에 도움 되는 말 주고받기  서로의 목표가 KPI, 즉 수치화 정량화가 가능한 형태로 되어있는지 알기 #  서로간에 팔로워를 한다던가 눌러주며, 서로가 하고 있는 영상이나 매체에 좋아요를 눌러주기</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joseph Rudyard Kipling, If</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Joseph-Rudyard-Kipling-If/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Joseph-Rudyard-Kipling-If/</guid>
      <description>Joseph Rudyard Kipling, If #  Who is he? #   1907년(42살) 최초 영어권 작가로서 노벨문학상을 받았음 운문, 산문에서 모두 인정 받음 제국주의 선지자로 불리기도 정글북의 동화작  That poem #    The Nation&amp;rsquo;s Favourite Poems. BBC. 1996. in UK  About &amp;lsquo;if&amp;rsquo; #  If you can keep your head when all about you Are losing theirs and blaming it on you,
아들아, 만약 네가 모든 것을 잃게 되더라도 용기를 잃지 않고, 그 잘못이 네게 있다는 걸 받아들인다면</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worried Heart Got Over by Meeting Napoleon Hill</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Worried-heart-got-over-by-meeting-napoleon-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 15:36:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Worried-heart-got-over-by-meeting-napoleon-hill/</guid>
      <description>희망을 보았다. #  책 속에 답이 있었다. 긍정하는 마음 자체가 결국 내게 필요했다는 생각이 든다.
사실, 부정적인 기분이 든다는 것 자체가, 내가 두려움에 떨어서 무너지고 있다는 신호이기도 했다.
두려움에 떤다는건 내가 무너지고 있다는 의미니까. 왜 두려움에 떤다는게 내가 무너지고 있다는걸 의미할까?
이는, 내 스스로 긍정적인 마음 자체가 사라지고 있다는 것을 의미했다. 긍정적인 마음. 뭔가를 올바르게 해내고 있지 못하다는 마음. 좋고, 풍요롭게 만드는 것들을 끌어당기는게 세상의 이치인데, 어느새인가 두려워하고, 불안해하는 마음이 안좋은 것들을 끌어당기게 둔다는 두려움.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automation physiology by Jarnet Pierre</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/automation-of-psycology-by-jarnet-pierre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/automation-of-psycology-by-jarnet-pierre/</guid>
      <description>J A- Boston Medical Library in the Francis A. County Library of Medicine ^ Boston Digitized by the Internet Archive in 2010 with funding from Open Knowledge Gommons and Harvard Medical School http: //www.archive.org/details/l**automatism**epsycOOjanePSYCHOLOGICAL AUTOMATION PSYCHOLOGICAL TEST OF EXPERIMENTAL PSYCHOLOGY ON LOWER FORMS OF HUMAN ACTIVITY BY PIERRE JANET Former student of the École normale supérieure Associate professor of philosophy at the Lycée du Havre Doctor of Letters. PARIS FORMER LIBRARY GERMER BAILLIÉRE ET G * FÉLIX ALCAN, PUBLISHER 108, BOULEVAKD SAINT-GERMAIN, 108 1889 All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decided on Learning C Language 2020</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Decided-on-learning-C-language-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 11:56:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/Decided-on-learning-C-language-2020/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ll get start to learn C language. #  Even I didn&amp;rsquo;t start or make any installation with that in this Linux laptop, but I believe there would be many profit for myself.
C language can be used in broad fields. #  As it&amp;rsquo;s called as a middle ware language, that can cover even in Embeded environment.
As I&amp;rsquo;m into permaculture, one day I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make the better enviroment construct by the installation of sensors in a place to optimize the growth of crops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think and grow rich transcribing cures me</title>
      <link>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/think-and-grow-rich-transcribing-cures-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 16:55:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sj-log.github.io/posts/think-and-grow-rich-transcribing-cures-me/</guid>
      <description>How to be rich even in spirituality. #  He does really great job and, no matter what it is, his book just shows me how to be the rich man in genuine term. Just having a lot of money in material isn&amp;rsquo;t a meaning of right form of Rich. The Rich that I think is, Materially, and spiritually being free. Of course, Being free almost can be achieved by materially Free, by a lot earning of money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
